哦不 我察觉到
Oh no I see
我被缠绕在蛛网中
A spider web it's tangled up with me
我失去了理智
And I lost my head
想起我曾说过的那些蠢话
The thought of all the stupid things I said
天哪 这都是些什么
Oh no what's this
我被困在蛛网之中
A spider web and I'm caught in the middle
我转身想要逃离
So I turned to run
想起我曾做过的那些傻事
The thought of all the stupid things I've done
我从未有意麻烦你
I never meant to cause you trouble
我从未有意伤害你
never meant to do you wrong
若我真的曾麻烦过你
If I ever caused you trouble
那也不是我所希望的
No I never meant to do you harm
哦 怎么会这样
Oh no I see
我被困在了蛛网之中
A spider web and it's me in the middle
我拼命想要挣脱
So I twist and turn
然而只是徒劳
Here am I in my little bubble
告诉你我从不想对你造成困扰
Singing out I never meant to cause you trouble
我从不想这样对你
No I never meant to do you wrong
若我真的曾麻烦过你
If I ever caused you trouble
那真的不是我所希望的
I never meant to do you harm
只是他们对我设下了陷阱
They spun a web for me
我从未有意麻烦你
I never meant to cause you trouble
我从未有意伤害你
never meant to do you wrong
若我真的曾麻烦过你
If I ever caused you trouble
那也不是我所希望的
No I never meant to do you harm
只是他们对我设下了陷阱
They spun a web for me
只是他们对我设下了陷阱……
They spun a web for me…